[{"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " hey-hey-hey. so what happened? a forest tick you off?", "answer": " no. y'know how we\u0092re always saying we need a place for the mail.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " yeah!", "answer": " well, i started building one. but then i decided to take it to the next step.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " you\u0092re building a post office?", "answer": " no, an entertainment unit, with a mail cubby built right in. it\u0092s a one day job, max.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " okay.  my word! those are snug.", "answer": " oh yeah. these are my old work pants, sergio valente\u0092s.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": "  hey pheebs.", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " any sign of your brother?", "answer": " no, but he\u0092s always late.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " i thought you only met him once?", "answer": " yeah, i did. i think it sounds y'know big sistery, y'know, \u0091frank\u0092s always late.\u0092", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " well relax, he\u0092ll be here.", "answer": " no, i know, i\u0092m just nervous. y'know it\u0092s just y'know mom\u0092s dead, don\u0092t talk to my sister, grandma\u0092s been sleeping a lot lately. it\u0092s like the last desperate chance to have a family, y'know, kinda thing. you\u0092re so sweet to wait with me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " does anyone else think david copperfield is cute?", "answer": " no, but he told me, he thinks your a fox.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " all right, janice, likes him. in fact she likes him so much she put him on her freebie list.", "answer": " her what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " well, we have a deal, where we each get to pick five celebrities that we can sleep with, and the other one can\u0092t get mad.", "answer": " ah, the heart of every healthy relationship. honesty, respect, and sex with celebrities.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " so, chandler, who\u0092s on your list?", "answer": " ah, kim basinger, cindy crawford, halle berry, yasmine bleeth, and ah, jessica rabbit.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " now, you do realize that she\u0092s a cartoon, and way out of your league?", "answer": " i know, i know, i just always wondered if i could get her eyes to pop out of her head.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " hey, monica, who would yours be?", "answer": " first, i need a boyfriend, then i can have a list.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " it\u0092s just a game mon.  rach, how about you?", "answer": " oh, i don\u0092t know, i guess, chris o\u0092donnel, john f. kennedy, jr., daniel day lewis, sting, and parker stevenson.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " spiderman?", "answer": " hardy boy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " peter parker.", "answer": " thank you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " what about you honey, who would be on your list?", "answer": " well i-i-i, that kind of thing requires some serious thought. first, i\u0092ll divide my perspective canidates into catergories....", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": "  what a geek!", "answer": "  everbody this is frank! this is my half-brother frank.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " oh, hi.", "answer": " this is everybody. this is ross.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " how are you?", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " chandler.", "answer": " hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " hi.", "answer": " joey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " hey-hey!", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " this is monica.", "answer": " whoa!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " and this is rachel.", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " whoa!!", "answer": " i\u0092m gonna get coffee.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " hey, how do you guys get anything done?", "answer": " we don\u0092t, really.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " well, so, now, do you guys have a lot of big plans?", "answer": " oh yeah! yeah, no, we\u0092re gonna connect, y'know bond, and everything.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " yeah, i was thinking that maybe we could go down to time square and pick up some ninja stars. and, oh, um, my friend larry, he wants me to take a picture of a hooker.", "answer": " you know, we don\u0092t really take advantage of living in the city.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " oh, i\u0092m sorry. did i get \u0091ya?", "answer": " no, you didn\u0092t get me!! it\u0092s an electric drill, you get me, you kill me!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " calm down, do you want this unit or not?", "answer": " i do not want this unit!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " well, you should\u0092ve told me that before, i\u0092m not a mind reader. hey, we\u0092re out of beer. i\u0092m going to monica\u0092s.", "answer": " fine!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " hey! where \u0091ya headin\u0092 in those pants? 1982?", "answer": " oh monica, listen, i ah, i saw down at the hardware store, they got those designer tiles on sale. if you ever want to redo the bathroom floor.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " why, what\u0092s wrong with my bathroom floor?", "answer": " nothing. it\u0092s just old and dingy, that\u0092s all.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " oh yeah. if you ah, move your hamper, you see what color the tile used to be.  yeah.", "answer": " i can\u0092t live like this! what are we gonna do? what are we gonna do?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " that\u0092s a little more than i wanted to see.", "answer": "  aw! look at that, every inch of this stuff is glued down. it\u0092d take forever to pry this up. you should ah, you should just leave it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " eh! there you go.", "answer": " you know that\u0092s nice, y'know we could put it back there after the surgeons remove it from your colon!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": "  oh, ew!", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " yeah i know what i wanted to ask you. um, can you roll your tongue? because i can, and my mom couldn\u0092t, and i thought y'know, i figured that was something i got from our dad.", "answer": " what, wait, you mean like this?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " your not doing it.", "answer": " oh right, yeah okay, my mom could, and i can\u0092t. we don\u0092t have that....", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " when\u0092s your birthday?", "answer": " feburary 16th.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " i know a guy who\u0092s the 18th.", "answer": " wow, that\u0092s close. when\u0092s yours?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " october 25th.", "answer": " that\u0092s the same month as halloween. so, um, what kinda things do you like to do at home?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " okay, i\u0092ve got three of my five.", "answer": " three of your five, what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " celebrities i\u0092m allowed to sleep with.", "answer": " oh my god! you are giving this a lot of thought.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " yeah, it\u0092s hard okay, i only have two spots left.", "answer": " all right, so who do you got it narrowed down to?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " okay, elizabeth hurely....", "answer": " oooh-hoo, very attractive, forgiving.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " susan sarandon.", "answer": " eh, y'know what, she\u0092s to political, she probably wouldn\u0092t let you do it, unless you donated four cans of food first.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " and!! isabella rosselini.", "answer": " ooh-hoo. very hot, very sexy. but ah, y'know she\u0092s too international, y'know she\u0092s never gonna be around.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " so?", "answer": " so, you gotta play the odds, pick somebody who\u0092s gonna be in the country like all the time.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " okay so, by melting, you meant melting.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " so is it like art?", "answer": " yeah, you can melt art. hey, can i use your phone?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " um, yeah sure. why you wanna call your mom?", "answer": " no, i wanna melt it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " oh, well um, not right now. y'know i\u0092m just gonna go to bed, i think the fumes are giving me a headache.", "answer": "  yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " g\u0092night, bro.", "answer": " g\u0092night.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " here.  y'know, just in case.", "answer": " oh, excellent.  commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " what kind of karate is that?", "answer": " no kind. he just makes it up.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " so how\u0092s it going with you guys?", "answer": " so far, it kinda blows. i don\u0092t know, i just thought y'know that he\u0092d feel more like a brother y'know, like you and ross, just like close and connected and....", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " oh honey, we\u0092re close now but you-you wouldn\u0092t believe the years of-of nugies, and wedgies, and flying wedgies, and atomic wedgies, and.... that\u0092s where the waistband actually goes over your head.", "answer": " ah!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " oh, we used to drive each other crazy playing the shadow game.", "answer": " oh, how do you play the shadow game?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " oh, how do you play the shadow game?", "answer": " i just asked you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " i just asked you.", "answer": " i don\u0092t have time for this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " no, that is what the game is.", "answer": " which you just gave up really quickly.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": "  have you seen joey?", "answer": " what\u0092s the matter?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " oh, just this!  y\u0092know what it\u0092s my fault really, because the couch is usually where we keep the varnish.", "answer": "  hey, does somebody wanna hand me one of those tiles.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " what\u0092s going on?", "answer": " he\u0092s retiling my floor.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " yo!! spackel boy! get up!", "answer": " ah-ah-ah, now you started this, you will finish it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " he started mine first!", "answer": " build the unit cinderelly, lay the tile cinderelly.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " whoa! big octopus.", "answer": " yeah.  \u0091hello.  oh my god, i totally forgot!  well can\u0092t someone else do it.  but, i have company.  yeah, no look, that\u0092s all right i\u0092ll come in.\u0092  um, frank, i\u0092m really sorry but i have to go to work. it\u0092s-it\u0092s one of my regulars and he\u0092s insisting that i do \u0091um.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " hey, what kind of work do you do?", "answer": " oh! i\u0092m a masseuse. i give people massages and stuff.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " you-you work at one of those massage parlors?", "answer": " well, y'know we don\u0092t call it that, but yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": "  wow! that\u0092s wild! no, i had no idea.", "answer": " all righty. i\u0092ll be back in-in a little bit. unless you wanna come with me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " you mean like watch?", "answer": " no, no, you can get one yourself. it\u0092ll be on the house! y'know what are big sisters for?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " well, i don\u0092t think this, y'know.", "answer": " no, no, no, i wouldn\u0092t do you myself, i mean that would be weird. yeah, no, i\u0092ll get one of the other girls to do it. oh, this will be so much fun! hey! are you excited?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " it\u0092s beautiful! it\u0092s like the first bathroom floor there ever was.  whoa! are you going in there for?", "answer": " what, like a number?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hi! bye!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " well, it\u0092s about time.", "answer": " ooh, very official.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " oh, yeah, well y'know chandler printed it up on his computer.", "answer": " and who laminated it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " that would be me.", "answer": " all right let me see.  uma thurman, winona ryder, elizabeth hurely, michelle pfieffer, and dorothy hammel?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " hey, it\u0092s my list.", "answer": " okay honey, you do realize she only spins like that on ice.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " ow!-ow!-ow! ow! ow! ow! ow! ow! ow! y'know, ow!", "answer": " hey!-hey! what\u0092s going on?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " she broke my arm.", "answer": " he touched my fanny.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " no, she touched mine first!", "answer": " that\u0092s my job!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " so wait, what\u0092s the deal here, i can have sex with you, but i can\u0092t touch you? phoebe and girl: ewww!!!", "answer": " you can\u0092t have sex with her!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " what\u0092d you think i was, a hooker?", "answer": " no, your a masseuse, it\u0092s cool, i\u0092m not a cop.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " okay, jasmine, can you, can you ask mr. whiffler if he can wait for like five minutes.", "answer": " fine.  i don\u0092t like you!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": "  so that\u0092s what you thought i did!! god! that\u0092s not what i do!", "answer": " wait that\u0092s-that\u0092s, what that\u0092s not what you do?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " nooo! why would you think that?", "answer": " i don\u0092t know, i mean, y'know, this is the city y'know, i just, i mean, i don\u0092t know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " whatever, it\u0092s the perfect end to the perfect weekend anyways.", "answer": " oh, wait, no your right, no it was perfect and i can\u0092t believe that i screwed it up so bad.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " you really thought it was perfect?", "answer": " well, no, maybe-maybe it wasn\u0092t perfect, but y'know it was pretty cool, y'know, \u0091cause we had all those great talks y'know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " yeah, um, which ones in particular were great for you?", "answer": " well y'know about the tongue thing, y'know, and how i told you about my likes and my dislikes...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " i don\u0092t....", "answer": " how-how i like to melt stuff, and how i dislike stuff that doesn\u0092t melt.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " right, okay, um-mm.", "answer": " yeah, y'know i feel like i can really talk to you \u0091cause y'know you\u0092re my sister, y'know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " yeah, i guess i do, yeah.", "answer": " then i go feel your friend up and make you mad at me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " well, i-i wasn\u0092t hopping mad, y'know.", "answer": " you hopped a little bit. yeah, i really sorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " okay. all right, this is my favourite part of the weekend, right now, this.", "answer": " this?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " uh-huh.", "answer": " oh come on we went, we went to time square, we found ninja stars, i almost got arm broken by a hooker...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " she wasn\u0092t a hooker.", "answer": " well, when i tell my friends about her she will be.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " okay, on three. one....two....", "answer": " why don\u0092t we just go on two.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " why two?", "answer": " because it\u0092s faster.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " yeah, i coulda counted to three like four times without all this \u0091two\u0092 talk.", "answer": " oh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " all right, but in the future...", "answer": " okay!! okay!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " come on!", "answer": " heavy thing, not getting lighter!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " okay, one...two...", "answer": " so we are going on two?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " oh, good job joe.", "answer": " wow, it\u0092s big!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " yeah-yeah, so big that it actually makes our doors look smaller!", "answer": " maybe, my ruler\u0092s wrong.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " maybe all the rulers are wrong.", "answer": " look it\u0092s not that bad. so what, it blocks a little of your door, a little of my door.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": "  thank you.", "answer": "  um, coffee to go, please. (ross recognises her and goes over to the couch, mouthing \u0091oh my god\u0092", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " are you serious?  oh my god.", "answer": " damn! i can\u0092t believe i took her off my list.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " why? \u0091cause otherwise you\u0092d go for it?", "answer": " yeah, maybe.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " oh-oh, you lie.", "answer": " what you don\u0092t think i\u0092d go up to her?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " ross, it took you ten years to finally admit you liked me.", "answer": " yeah, well missy, you better be glad that list is laminated.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " you know what honey, you go ahead, we\u0092ll call her an alternate.", "answer": " okay, hold my crawler.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " rach, are you really gonna let him do this?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " honey, he\u0092s about to go hit on isabella rosselini. i\u0092m just sorry we don\u0092t got popcorn.", "answer": "  hi! hi, i\u0092m ross, you don\u0092t know me, but i\u0092m a big, big fan of yours. i mean, blue velvet, woo-oo hoo! um, i was wondering if i could um, maybe buy you a cup of coffee?  or maybe reimburse you for that one?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " well, yeah, kinda. um, but that\u0092s okay, see we have an understanding, um, see we each have this list of five famous people,  so i\u0092m allowed to sleep with you. no, no, no, it\u0092s flattery.", "answer": " i\u0092m sorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " oh no, no, no, wait, wait, isabella. don\u0092t, don\u0092t just dismiss this so fast. i mean this is a once in a lifetime opportunity...", "answer": " yeah, for you. is that the list?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " um, yeah.", "answer": " may i see it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " um, no.", "answer": " come on!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " but, okay.", "answer": "  i\u0092m not on the list!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " um, see, but that\u0092s not the final draft.", "answer": " it\u0092s laminated!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " yeah, um, okay see, you were, you were on the list but my friend, chandler  brought up the very good point that you are international, so i bumped you for wynona rider, local.", "answer": " y'know it\u0092s ironic...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " ...because i have a list of five goofy coffee house guys and yesterday i bumped you for that guy over there.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": " y'know what?", "answer": " umm?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 287, "asentId": 288}, {"question": " i\u0092ve got five bucks says you can\u0092t.", "answer": " get out your checkbook, mister.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 291, "asentId": 292}, {"question": " you are dogged man! i totally fit!", "answer": " yeah, you got me.  i\u0092m out five big ones!  here you go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 295, "asentId": 296}]